{
  "customWordGroups": [
    {
      "group": "1stGrade",
      "words": [
        {
          "front": "must",
          "back": "You must pay attention!"
        },
        {
          "front": "new",
          "back": "She got him a new coat."
        },
        {
          "front": "no",
          "back": "She shook her head no."
        },
        {
          "front": "now",
          "back": "You must be very hungry now."
        },
        {
          "front": "on",
          "back": "There is an apple on the table."
        },
        {
          "front": "our",
          "back": "Our school is very large."
        },
        {
          "front": "out",
          "back": "She went out to buy some food."
        },
        {
          "front": "please",
          "back": "Please sit down."
        },
        {
          "front": "pretty",
          "back": "Her pink dress was very pretty."
        },
        {
          "front": "ran",
          "back": "The cat ran out of the house."
        },
        {
          "front": "ride",
          "back": "He took his horse for a ride."
        },
        {
          "front": "saw",
          "back": "She saw him at school."
        },
        {
          "front": "say",
          "back": "Go say goodbye to them."
        },
        {
          "front": "she",
          "back": "She is a great friend."
        },
        {
          "front": "so",
          "back": "I missed the bus, so I had to walk home."
        },
        {
          "front": "soon",
          "back": "I hope that she'll get well soon."
        },
        {
          "front": "that",
          "back": "That is my pencil."
        },
        {
          "front": "there",
          "back": "There was a light rain yesterday."
        },
        {
          "front": "they",
          "back": "They are nice people."
        },
        {
          "front": "this",
          "back": "I will give you this book."
        },
        {
          "front": "all",
          "back": "I gave her all the books I had."
        },
        {
          "front": "am",
          "back": "I am tired."
        },
        {
          "front": "are",
          "back": "How are you?"
        },
        {
          "front": "at",
          "back": "She looked at me."
        },
        {
          "front": "ate",
          "back": "We ate cake after dinner."
        },
        {
          "front": "be",
          "back": "She grew up to be a doctor."
        },
        {
          "front": "black",
          "back": "He had dark black hair."
        },
        {
          "front": "brown",
          "back": "She has brown eyes."
        },
        {
          "front": "but",
          "back": "We had no choice but to leave."
        },
        {
          "front": "came",
          "back": "He came to my house yesterday."
        },
        {
          "front": "did",
          "back": "He did a lot for us."
        },
        {
          "front": "do",
          "back": "We should do something special today."
        },
        {
          "front": "eat",
          "back": "They like to eat at home."
        },
        {
          "front": "four",
          "back": "I leave each day at four."
        },
        {
          "front": "get",
          "back": "Did you get my message?"
        },
        {
          "front": "good",
          "back": "The car is in good condition."
        },
        {
          "front": "have",
          "back": "I have a cat."
        },
        {
          "front": "he",
          "back": "He loves me."
        },
        {
          "front": "into",
          "back": "She came into the room."
        },
        {
          "front": "like",
          "back": "I like cake."
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "group": "AM_word_family",
      "words": [
        {
          "front": "ham",
          "back": "We're having ham for dinner."
        },
        {
          "front": "jam",
          "back": "I like biscuits with jam."
        },
        {
          "front": "am",
          "back": "I am happy."
        },
        {
          "front": "slam",
          "back": "Please don't slam the door."
        },
        {
          "front": "gram",
          "back": "The gram is a metric unit."
        },
        {
          "front": "clam",
          "back": "A clam is a freshwater mussel."
        },
        {
          "front": "ram",
          "back": "A male sheep is called a ram."
        },
        {
          "front": "yam",
          "back": "I had a roasted yam for lunch."
        },
        {
          "front": "says",
          "back": "Don't believe a word he says."
        },
        {
          "front": "of",
          "back": "He is a friend of mine."
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "group": "words_ending_in_ck",
      "words": [
        {
          "front": "pick",
          "back": "Please pick a color."
        },
        {
          "front": "sock",
          "back": "I have one pink sock."
        },
        {
          "front": "neck",
          "back": "What animal has a very long neck?"
        },
        {
          "front": "lock",
          "back": "He forgot to lock the car."
        },
        {
          "front": "trick",
          "back": "Trick or treat."
        },
        {
          "front": "clock",
          "back": "I have an alarm clock."
        },
        {
          "front": "rock",
          "back": "I have a rock garden."
        },
        {
          "front": "lick",
          "back": "Could I have a lick of your ice cream?"
        },
        {
          "front": "find",
          "back": "We need to find the matching shoe!"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "group": "ay_word_family",
      "words": [
        {
          "front": "may",
          "back": "May I have a cookie?"
        },
        {
          "front": "pay",
          "back": "She received a small pay increase."
        },
        {
          "front": "gray",
          "back": "It was a gray winter day."
        },
        {
          "front": "day",
          "back": "Friday is a great day!"
        },
        {
          "front": "play",
          "back": "Rain held up play for an hour."
        },
        {
          "front": "tray",
          "back": "She carried the tray of food to our table."
        },
        {
          "front": "way",
          "back": "The back way was blocked."
        },
        {
          "front": "lay",
          "back": "Please lay your books on the table."
        },
        {
          "front": "come",
          "back": "Please come here."
        },
        {
          "front": "from",
          "back": "Jane is from Ohio."
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "group": "op_word_family",
      "words": [
        {
          "front": "top",
          "back": "They live on the top floor of the building."
        },
        {
          "front": "mop",
          "back": "Spills can be wiped up with a damp mop."
        },
        {
          "front": "stop",
          "back": "Stop that man!"
        },
        {
          "front": "flop",
          "back": "It fell to the ground with a flop."
        },
        {
          "front": "pop",
          "back": "I can pop back in later."
        },
        {
          "front": "shop",
          "back": "Where do you like to shop?"
        },
        {
          "front": "plop",
          "back": "I love to plop down on the sofa."
        },
        {
          "front": "drop",
          "back": "Be careful not to drop the cup."
        },
        {
          "front": "any",
          "back": "Do you have any books?"
        },
        {
          "front": "would",
          "back": "Would you like to play?"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "group": "words_ending_in_at",
      "words": [
        {
          "front": "bat",
          "back": "I hit the ball with the bat."
        },
        {
          "front": "cat",
          "back": "I have a cat."
        },
        {
          "front": "that",
          "back": "Was the book that bad?"
        },
        {
          "front": "fat",
          "back": "They made a big fat profit last year."
        },
        {
          "front": "sat",
          "back": "I sat next to my mom."
        },
        {
          "front": "mat",
          "back": "We sleep on mats on the floors."
        },
        {
          "front": "pat",
          "back": "She gave the dog a quick pat."
        },
        {
          "front": "hat",
          "back": "I love my pink hat."
        },
        {
          "front": "teacher",
          "back": "My teacher is nice."
        },
        {
          "front": "are",
          "back": "Are we there yet?"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "group": "in_word_family",
      "words": [
        {
          "front": "win",
          "back": "They didn't win the game."
        },
        {
          "front": "thin",
          "back": "Her coat was too thin."
        },
        {
          "front": "tin",
          "back": "She bought a tin of soup."
        },
        {
          "front": "chin",
          "back": "He rubbed the stubble on his chin."
        },
        {
          "front": "pin",
          "back": "A PIN is a secret number."
        },
        {
          "front": "bin",
          "back": "My dad took out the recycling bin."
        },
        {
          "front": "grin",
          "back": "She had a big grin on her face."
        },
        {
          "front": "spin",
          "back": "He puts a new spin on the story."
        },
        {
          "front": "you",
          "back": "You may have a cookie."
        },
        {
          "front": "orange",
          "back": "I like the color orange."
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "group": "an_word_family",
      "words": [
        {
          "front": "ban",
          "back": "My parents will ban shoes in the house."
        },
        {
          "front": "can",
          "back": "She can speak French well."
        },
        {
          "front": "than",
          "back": "I like donuts better than cake."
        },
        {
          "front": "man",
          "back": "He is an honest man."
        },
        {
          "front": "pan",
          "back": "I have a stainless steel pan."
        },
        {
          "front": "tan",
          "back": "They tan easily in the summer."
        },
        {
          "front": "span",
          "back": "A decade will span 10 years."
        },
        {
          "front": "van",
          "back": "He drives a small delivery van."
        },
        {
          "front": "done",
          "back": "The cake should be done soon."
        },
        {
          "front": "white",
          "back": "He was wearing white sneakers."
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
